{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How many sides are there in a pentagon?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "4",
                "5",
                "6",
                "7"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is: 16 x 16 = ?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "192",
                "252",
                "256",
                "264"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How many sides are there in a octagon?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "5",
                "6",
                "7",
                "8"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What is: 361 / 19 = ?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "19",
                "17",
                "20.056",
                "18.05"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How many sides are there in a star?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "10",
                "11",
                "12",
                "14"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is: 21 x 17 = ?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "273",
                "331",
                "336",
                "357"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "How many sides are there in a heptagon?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "3",
                "5",
                "7",
                "9"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is: 84 / 4 = ?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "16",
                "18",
                "21",
                "24"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How many sides are there in a triange?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "3",
                "4",
                "5",
                "6"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is: 11 x 7 = ?",
            "answerOptions": [
                "71",
                "77",
                "78",
                "79"
            ],
            "answerIndex": 1
        }
    ]
}